本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
我说你们大家想不想看点特别有趣的东西
Hey, you guys want to see something funny?
哦  如果又是你掀起自己衣服
Oh, if this is where you lift your shirt up.
露出肚脐眼跳肚皮舞那套  还是算了吧
And make your belly button sing... no, thank you.
比那还要好呢  给你们看看我给小查莉剪的视频呀
Even better. Check out this video I made of Charlie.
做个宝宝真不爽
Being a baby stinks.
食物总是太糊太糙又太稀了
Food's too mushy, gross and too juicy,
还有大人们给我看的电视节目都很粗鲁无礼
And the tv shows they make me watch are insulting.
啊  这下好多了
Ahh, much better.
生活真美好
Life is good.
完
儿子  你一定要把这段上传到网上给你们外婆看看
P.J., you are gonna have to put that online so grandma can see it.
外婆会上网的啊
Grandma knows how to go online?
儿子  你得把这刻成光碟
P.J., you're gonna have to put that on a DVD
寄给外婆看
So grandma can watch it.
外婆有光碟播放机吗
Grandma got a DVD. Player?
好吧  儿子  你亲自去趟外婆家
Okay, P.J., you're just gonna have to go over to grandma's house.
把这放给外婆看吧
And act it out for her.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
■
翻译： 山鹰逢羽
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
■
校订  后期： WaitinZ  love0forever
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第十五集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E15  Charlie Goes Viral
好  念这句  图书馆在哪儿
Okay, where is the library?
（注：法语音节）
突苏馆在哪哎
Donde esta la libraria?
哈哈  你说卷舌儿话音节时真是好迷人
Okay, you're really cute when you roll your rs,
（注：西班牙语音节）
可应该这样念  比不里泰卡
But it's "Biblioteca."
比不利泰卡
Biblioteca.
不过再念一次“突苏馆”给我听吧
But say "Libraria" Again.
突苏苏馆馆馆儿 儿 儿
Libraria.
你这样念真是让我好有感觉呀
Your rrrs make me all Mmm.
对了  我要问你点事
Hey, listen, I want to ask you something.
唔  听上去很有意思  是什么呢
Ooh, that sounds interesting. What is it?
那个嘛
Well...
盖比  打扰一下
Gabe, do you mind?
没关系  你们可以留在这儿
No, you can stay.
我们还是上楼去吧
Let's go upstairs.
好主意  我本来想叫你们走的
Good idea. I was gonna say something,
不过不想显得没礼貌而已
But I didn't want to be rude.
好了  现在可以告诉我是什么事了吧
Okay, now what did you want to ask me?
我想问你
I was wondering if...
你真是太让我丢脸了
It was embarrassing.
我只是问个很简单的问题呀
It was a simple question.
你爸隔了两个通道对我喊
Your father shouts at me from two aisles away,
喂  艾米  你想选什么样的厕纸啊
"Hey, ames, what kind of toilet paper you like...
两层纸面还是超多层纸面的
Quilted or super-quilted?"
嘿  快看  斯宾塞来做客了
Hey, look, Spencer's here.
所以呢  全世界并不知道
So what, the world doesn't know.
伟大的艾米·邓肯也会使用厕纸呀
That the great Amy Duncan uses toilet paper?
邓肯先生  邓肯太太  见到你们很高兴
Nice to see you, Mr. And Mrs. Duncan.
你那么大喊了一通后  居然还是拿错了我们要的种类
After all that shouting, you got the wrong kind.
因为我本来就不是厕纸通灵大师
Well, that's because I'm not Bob the toilet paper psychic.
还是去那边吧
Right this way.
好吧  破罐子破摔
Well, on the bright side,
你也拿错了垃圾袋
You got the wrong trash bags too.
我替我父母道歉了
Sorry about my parents.
哇  我好像常常替他们道歉
Wow, I say that a lot.
那我想问你的是
So what I wanted to ask you was...
我要抓住你咯  我一定会抓住你
I'm gonna get you! I'm gonna get you!
抓住了  抓住了
Yes, I am. Yes, I am.
要抓住了
Yes, I am.
好了  我们还是去屋外吧
Okay, let's go outside.
他要抓住她还早得很呢
It usually takes him a while to get her.
行了  我想我已经甩掉所有的家庭成员了
Okay, I think I'm all out of family members,
不过你最好还是快点讲完
But you'd better talk fast.
行  我是想说
Okay, I was wondering.
你在礼拜五能不能穿上我的橄榄球球衣呢
If you would wear my football Jersey on Friday.
这是球队选手女朋友们的一个惯例
It's sort of a tradition that the players' girlfriends.
要在比赛日穿着队员男友的球衣去
Wear their jerseys on game day.
那这样意思就是说我已经是你的
So that would make me.
女朋友了吗
Your girlfriend?
对呀
Yeah.
太好了
Cool
因为我还不是很确定我们的关系到底是怎样
Because I wasn't exactly sure of our status.
而且我又好紧张怕去问你
And I was too nervous to ask.
我不想成为那种没水准的女生
And I didn't want to be one of those girls.
非要逼着你说出来  不过话说回来
That made you talk about it. But then again...
那你是答应穿球衣了吧
So that's a yes on the Jersey?
当然啦  我的男友
Of course it's a yes, boyfriend.
我要回商店去
Back to the store,
把那正确的超级多层厕纸给换回来
Where the correct answer was super-quilted!
哇  太强大了  查莉的那个视频火起来了
Whoa, this is amazing. That Charlie video has gone viral.
啥叫火起来了
What does that mean?
自从上星期二以来  已经有百万人次的点击率了
That it's gotten a million hits since last Tuesday.
现在我再回答你接下来的问题
And now I'll answer your next question.
那意思就是有一百万的人已经看过我们家查莉了
That means over a million people have seen it.
所以你是把那视频发到“脸酷”上去了么
So what, you put that on the FaceTube?
（注：老爸把Facebook和YouTube搞混了）
说的好  老爸  就是“脸酷”啊
Yeah, that's right, dad... the FaceTube.
我要上电视啰
I'm gonna be on tv.
啥
What?
有线新闻八台刚才打电话来了
The Channel 8 News just called.
因为那视频在全世界网络上传播开了
And now that this video is allver the Internet,
他们想给“臭屁宝宝查莉”一家做一个详细追踪报道
They want to do an exclusive on the "Farty Charlie" family.
那不是我们全体都要上电视了
So we're all gonna be on tv
对  我就是想告诉你们来着
That's what I meant.
这边是我们家的起居室
And this is our family room.
你们家什么来着
Your family what?
起居室儿儿呀
Our family rrroom.
这里真是安静祥和呀
Oh, it's so nice and peaceful here.
对呀  这房子很大  但是只有我爸妈和我三口人住
Well, it's a big house and it's just me, mom and dad.
天  太美好了
Oh, how wonderful.
爸妈  她是泰迪
Mom, dad, this is Teddy.
您好  很高兴认识你们  华尔士先生和太太
Hi, nice to meet you, Mr. And Mrs. Walsh.
别客气  我是琳达  我先生保罗
Oh, please, I'm Linda. This is Paul.
斯宾塞老是不停口的跟我们说起你
Spencer has told us so much about you.
你比他讲的还要漂亮多了
You're even prettier than he said.
爸爸快别说了
Dad, stop.
哎呀不要紧的  我一点不介意被人家说漂亮
Oh, no, it's okay. I don't mind being pretty.
对了  斯宾塞  趁我没忘跟你说呀
Oh, Spence, before I forget,
你妈妈今天在商场做了件特可爱的事
Your mom did the cutest thing in the store today.
她指着一个形状像爱心的茄子
She pointed out an eggplant in the shape of a heart.
说那让她想起了我
And said it remded her of me.
我说的是真的呀
Well, it did.
他们一定和我家爸妈不在一个商场买东西
They must shop at a different store than my parents.
好了  等我赶快放下这些东西给你们俩孩子弄些小零食吃
Well, let me put these away and I'll fix you kids a quick snack.
哦  那吉他真是很漂亮
Oh, that's a beautiful guitar.
哎呀  谢谢你  这是我们上次去西班牙旅行时我买来的
Oh, thank you. I picked this up on our last trip to Spain.
我可以弹奏给你们听吗
Do you mind if I play?
请便
No, go ahead.
我习惯了  我那老哥  成天都弹吉他的而且他弹的啊
Yeah, my brother... he plays guitar and he...
从来没这么好听过  哦  真是太美妙了
Sounds nothing like that. Oh, that is so pretty.
谢谢  泰迪  请坐下慢慢欣赏吧
Thank you. Teddy, have a seat, relax.
好的
Okay.
喔唷  是按摩椅
Oh, massage chair.
舒服啊
Ni-I-I-ce.
烟熏三文鱼和蘸酱切边吐司
Smoked salmon and dill on toast points.
您这弄的算小零食吗
That's a snack?
我个人对厨艺烹调稍有涉猎
I dabble in the culinary arts.
您这手艺可是比稍有涉猎强多了
Mm, you more than dabble in that.
哦等等  我能再拿一块吗
Oh wait, can I have one more?
你想现在开始学习不
You want to start studying?
再等一分钟就好
In a mi-I-inute.
哼  我早就知道了  一旦人到达巅峰
Well, I'm not surprised. Once you're on top,
总有人嫉妒的想把你拉下马
They just want to knock you down.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你来看看有些人对查莉的视频的回复评论吧
Listen to some of these comments about the Charlie video.
这个叫Fredr5178的人说
Fred r5178 says,
“可爱是可爱  不过这只是狗屎运  昙花一现的”
"Cute, but you got lucky, one-hit wonder."
还有另外一个人说“你真是个可悲没天赋的失败者”
Here's another one... "You're a pathetic, no-talent loser!"
后面还跟了十九个惊叹号
With about 19 exclamation points.
这人账号名字叫“盖比D”
That one's from GabeD.
这些人到底是谁啊
Who are these people?
那可没办法查得出来
There's no way to know.
盖比宝贝  过来这边
Gabe honey, come here.
给你看看妈妈以前的风光时刻
I want to show you something very exciting from mommy's past.
老姐告诉过我只要听到那种话
Teddy told me if I ever heard those words,
应该直接忽视走掉
I should just keep walking.
给我留在这儿
Park it.
我现在是为了上电视前的准备功课
Now in preparation for our television appearance
先翻出以前的我以前做的传播节目来研究一下
I'm studying some of my previous broadcast work.
想当年老娘也是记者一名
I used to be a reporter.
是西南丹佛社区学院的时事新闻组成员
For the southwest Denver community college action news team.
在全国都有我们成打的观众群呢
We reached dozens of viewers all across the country.
现在放的这个是我最有力的报道之一
This is one of my hardest-hitting pieces.
在我手里拿着的这个东西
In my hand I'm holding.
是我们校园中首次登场的
Something new to our campus...
手机
A cell phone.
就是移动电话的简称
"Cell" Is short for "Cellular"
信不信由你
Believe it or not,
你可以随处带着这个电话到处跑
You can use this phone wherever you go.
我知道这听上去很无稽
I know it sounds crazy,
（注：90年代美国著名歌手）
不过正如宝拉·阿布杜会说的
But as Paula abdul would say,
“我是实话实说”
"I'm tellin' ya straight up."
真是不错  老娘太牛了
It was good. It was really good.
-晕  无法相信  -没开玩笑吧  史上最差投球
- Oh, unbelievable. - Are you kidding me? That's the worst throw!
喂
Hi.
哦  泰迪啊  你手里拿的是什么
Hey, Teddy. Hey, what you got there?
从斯宾塞家里拿来的打包饭菜
Leftovers from Spencer's house.
快点啊
Come on!
我看不下去了  我要关了它
I can't watch this. I'm turning it off.
别别  等等  广告是那个会说话的搞笑大脚呢
No no, wait wait. The commercial with the talking foot.
吃饭啦
Dinner!
（注：buns也是俚语中的“臀部”）
拿着你的圆面包  今晚吃牛肉三明治
Grab your buns. It's sloppy Joe night.
妈妈刚才说“拿着你的屁股”哈哈
Mom just said, "Grab your buns."
最好快去拿  泰迪
Go fast.Teddy.
我不用了  谢谢
I'm fine, thank you.
喔  你吃的是啥
Ooh, what are you having?
蘸酱切边吐司配三文鱼
Toast points with salmon and dill.
切边吐司  要我说管它切不切都是一样吃
Toast points? I say what's-the-points.
嘿  快看小查莉
Hey, check out Charlie.
她把牛肉酱涂脸上去了
She put sloppy Joe on her face.
因为她是个宝宝  这有什么可笑的
Because she's a baby. What's so funny?
并不因为她是宝宝才可笑
It's not just funny 'cause she's a baby.
看到了吧  老少皆宜
See, this works on all ages.
好了盖比  你知道不该这么做
Now Gabe, you know that's not right.
就是  你还做的不够地道呢
Yeah, it should be more like this.
好了好了  都停下
Okay, all right, all right, cut it out.
谁再敢扔牛肉酱的
Next person who throws sloppy Joe...
你们知道吗  在斯宾塞家吃饭时
Guys, you know, at Spencer's house.
他们的食物是直接从盘子里吃到嘴里的
The food goes directly from their plates to their mouths.
那有什么好玩的
How is that fun?
我明晚再告诉你
I'll let you know tomorrow night
因为明天我还是要过去吃晚饭
because I'm going over there for dinner.
她妈妈要烹制鹌鹑  不是肉酱哦  是真的鹌鹑
His mom is making quail. Not sloppy quail... quail.
你明晚不能去那边吧
You can't go over there tomorrow night.
有线八台新闻组要过来采访啊
The channel 8 news crew is coming over.
他们是要采访我们全家人的
They're gonna interview the whole family.
行了  我看我还是不出席吧
Yeah, I think I'll pass.
什么  你不想和我一起上电视吗
What, you don't want to be on tv with me?
还有我们呢
Us.
对  我们
Us?
不要  我可不想成为什么“臭屁查莉”家的一份子
No, I don't want to be a part of the "Farty charlie" Family.
好丢脸的称号
It's embarrassing.
你是说称号丢脸呢
还是说我们让你丢脸
Or we're embarrassing?
我就是那意思
Yes.
我们还要来点牛肉酱
More for us.
没问题
Yep.
我可不允许有人说PJ·邓肯只是一闪而逝的流星
Nobody calls P.J. Duncan a one-hit wonder.
来看“查莉臭屁第二弹”
Behold "Farty Charlie II."
PJ·邓肯为您呈现
PJ·邓肯执导电影
查莉臭屁2：卷土重来
大家好  我是查莉  我今天觉得特别胀气
Hey, I'm Charlie. I'm feeling extra gassy today.
哎呀  要放了哦
Uh-oh, here comes.
哈  这下好多了
Ahh, that's better.
那你觉得这段做的怎么样
So what do you think?
真不知从哪儿开始说
Where do I begin?
那个根本都不是查莉  是个娃娃啦
That wasn't even Charlie. That was a doll.
因为查莉在睡午觉啊
Because Charlie had to take a nap.
还有  要不是因为她是你妹妹  你才看不出来
Plus, you can only tell 'cause you're her brother.
才怪  我看出来是因为那娃娃的脚都装反了
No, I could tell because her foot was facing the wrong direction.
好了  你到底喜不喜欢这一段
Well, did you like anything about it?
呃  我喜欢那个
Well, I liked...
不喜欢
No.
晕  网友们说对了  我就是个不长久的流星
Man, the people are right. I am a one-hit wonder.
往好处想  你至少有过辉煌的时刻呀
Look, you had a good run.
才三十秒呀
30 seconds?
本来我是想帮丑猪涂涂口红看你能不能变俏的
Look, I'm trying to put lipstick on a pig here.
不过你根本就是朽木不可雕也
You're a failure.
丑猪涂口红  哈哈真好笑
Lipstick on a pig... that's hilarious.
我有灵感做下一个视频了
I just got an idea for my next film.
要是有人找我
If anyone needs me,
就说我去了杂货店和动物园
I'll be at the drugstore, then the zoo.
哦  亲爱的  泰迪来了  咱儿子在哪呢
Oh, honey, it's Teddy. Where's Spence?
啊  他要过两个小时候才会回来呀
Oh, he won't be back for a couple of hours.
哦  我是不是来早了
Oh, am I early?
搞不好我碰巧来的太早了
Did I accidentally come here too early.
不小心的
By mistake somehow?
不要紧
It's fine.
我也可以在外面等的
Because I could wait outside.
别傻了  快进来坐吧  你就当自己家一样
Oh, don't be silly. Go on, have a seat. Make yourself at home.
那张椅子也会振动吗
Oh, does that one vibrate too?
不是啊  只有那张是按摩椅
No, just that one.
哦
Oh
那你想坐那张椅子吗
Would you prefer that one?
嘿嘿  这主意不错
Hey, there's an idea.
你觉得怎么样  亲爱的
So how are you, dear?
这个么  既然您问了
Well, now that you ask,
我有点嘴馋呢
I'm a little snacky.
真舒服
Ahh.
我就是视频导演PJ·邓肯  这位是我的助理盖比
P.J. Duncan, director; This is Gabe, entourage.
你好  我是瑞克·科尔曼  有线八台新闻频道的
Hi, I'm Rick Coleman, channel 8 news.
告诉你  我已经有很多超过瘾的大拍摄计划就要公布了
Listen, I've got a lot of exciting new projects coming up,
所以如果你等一会儿注意提起“猪”或“口红”的关键词
So if you could mention the words "Pig" Or "Lipstick,"
你应该能搞到些独家新闻
You might get yourself an exclusive.
你好  她就是查莉  我是鲍伯
Hi, this is Charlie. I'm Bob.
是“鲍伯灭害公司”的么
Of "Bob's bugs be gone."
对呀  难道你在城里见过我的灭害专车吗
Yeah. You've seen my trucks around town?
因为我看到你衣服上的一个大虫子
And the big bug on your shirt.
哎呀我都没注意到自己穿了这件呢
Oh, didn't even realize I was wearing this.
你女儿也穿了件一模一样的
Or that she's wearing the exact same shirt.
哟  你可啥也不知道
Hey, what do you know?
大家好
Hi, everybody.
我是艾米  查莉的妈妈
I'm Amy, Charlie's mom.
同时也是“早安校园”节目的前主播
And former anchor for "Good Morning Campus Today."
我跟你说啊  拍摄时你要是有问题
Listen, if you run into any problems.
在你那接不上的话  只要转给我就行
During your segment, just throw it to me.
我可以成为你的好搭档的
I'll be your go-to gal.
亲爱的  你有没有排练过介绍自己业务的台词呀
Honey, have you rehearsed what you're gonna say about your business?
还要排演啊  我可以张口即来的
Rehearsed? I'm just gonna wing it.
不行不行  老公  你临场发挥一向不太好
No no, Bob, you're not very good at winging it.
你还记得结婚时你怎么说誓言的么
Remember your wedding vows?
“我 喜 欢 欢 她”
"I like her."
亲爱的  那时我是有点紧张
Honey, I was a little nervous.
可这都是八百年前的事了  我现在肯定没问题
And that was a long time ago. I'm gonna be fine.
我说妈妈  你脸上好像有什么东西
Hey, mom, you have something on your face.
在哪里
Oh, where?
整张脸都是
Everywhere.
宝贝  上电视是要画浓妆的
Honey, you need to wear a lot of makeup on television.
这样你在灯光下才不会看上去太惨淡
So that you're not washed out under all the lights.
小孩们不懂这些  因为他们没从事媒体这行
The kids don't know this because they're not in the media arts.
我是不知道您是多久以前
I don't know how long it's been.
从事的媒体行业
Since you've been in the media arts,
不过现在高清台直播都不打强光的
But with hi-def you don't need a lot of light.
这样啊  那我的妆在高清下效果会怎么样
Oh, well, how will my makeup look in hi-def?
应该蛮有趣的
Should be interesting.
好了  我们开始吧
Okay, let's do this.
瑞克·科尔曼为您报道
This is Rick Coleman,
我现在与邓肯家最潮流的网络红人在一起
And I'm here with Denver's newest celebrity.
有电脑的人们一定都很熟悉她的面孔了
Who's been seen by, well, pretty much everyone with a computer.
她可爱又有趣
She's cute. She's funny.
她就是臭屁查莉
She's farty Charlie!
话筒交还给你  瑞克
Back to you, Rick.
这张是去年夏天我们家族在亚斯本聚会时拍的
And here we are on our family reunion last summer in Aspen.
你们住在木屋里哦
You were staying in a lodge?
不是  那个是我们家的舱屋
No, that's our cabin.
我们家的木屋是在我家那座山的另外一边
Our lodge is on the other side of our mountain.
爸别说了  你说的好像我们家很有钱似的
Dad, stop. You're making us sound like we're rich.
其实我们并没有拥有自己的山啦
We don't have our own mountain.
是和另外一家人共同拥有的
We share it with another family.
既然说到家人了  泰迪  我们什么时候能见见你家人呢
Speaking of families, Teddy, when are we gonna get to meet yours?
哎呀  他们比较忙
Uh, they're kind of busy,
可能明年夏天才有空
So maybe next summer.
不然后年好了
Or the one after that.
大家听我说  我在厨房看到一个有趣的新闻
Okay, everyone, I have the news on in the kitchen.
你们一定要看看这些人
You have got to see these people.
当他们看到我在第一线的出色工作表现后
And when they saw what great work I was doing out in the field,
他们说"我们今日早安校园就一定需要这样的人才"
they said, "Hey, we need her on 'good morning campus today.'"
瑞克  你可以这样说
Rick, you might say.
这是我无法拒绝的工作邀请呀
It was an offer I couldn't refuse.
我们还是回到查莉的话题
If we could get back to Charlie...
不如来和这位骄傲的父亲聊一聊
Why don't we talk to the proud papa?
呼呼
Whew.
哇  老爸  你身上的汗都把衣服弄湿了
Whoa, look, dad, you're sweating right through your shirt.
呃
Uh...
瑞克  你知道
You know, Rick,
我发现了什么有意思的事吗
Something I find very interesting.
手机现在真是越来越小了
Is that cell phones have gotten so much smaller.
交回给你了  瑞克
Back to you, Rick.
好吧  PJ  你就是这个小短片的导演
So, PJ, you're the director of this little epic.
对  瑞克  我是导演  编剧  剪辑  配音全包
That's right, rick... director, writer, editor and voice.
我不知道制片是干啥的
I don't know what a producer does,
不过那肯定也是我干的活
But I probably did that too.
你要做什么啊
What are you doing?
好了  你只要把话筒给我  我会把话题抛给你的
Well, you just give it to me and I'll throw it back to you.
不用了
No, we're done.
至少我也可以交还给摄制棚里的尤兰达
At least let me throw it back to Yolanda in the studio.
行了  我自己会做  现在转回棚内的尤兰达
No, I do that. Back to Yolanda in the studio.
你们这些家伙脑子有病啊
What is wrong with you people?
我就知道你们肯定爱看
I thought you'd enjoy that.
你可绝对想不到
You have no idea.
这什么怪家庭啊  那个女人
What a family. The woman...
看上去像个马戏团的小丑
She looks like a circus clown.
小丑很有趣呀
Clowns are fun.
还有那个汗湿大块头原始族  他也算搞笑
What about the big sweaty oaf? He was a piece of work.
原始族也很好玩呀
Oafs are fun.
他们从哪里挖出这些怪胎的
Where did they find these people?
爸妈  别说了行吗  那是泰迪的家人
Mom, dad, stop, okay? That's Teddy's family.
这笑话不错  斯宾塞
That's a good one, Spence.
不  他不是开玩笑
No, he's not kidding.
可是泰迪  你跟他们一点都不一样
Oh, but Teddy, you're nothing like those people.
你这么稳重高雅
You're so poised and sophisticated and...
不好意思
Excuse me?
我说
I said...
我可以这样做因为我也是邓肯家的人
I can do that because I'm a Duncan.
我是那个汗湿原始人和疯颠颠小丑的生出的孩子
I'm the product of the sweaty oaf and the crazy clown.
哎呀  泰迪  对不起  我们不晓得
Oh Teddy, I'm sorry. We didn't know.
哦  不用道歉  没关系  昨天我也觉得他们很丢脸
Oh, no no, it's okay. Yesterday I was embarrassed by them too.
我甚至这样跟他们说了  然后我到你们家来
And I even told them that. And then I came over here.
可以假装自己是你们的一份子
So I could pretend that I was one of you.
可我并不是你们  我属于他们
But I'm not. I'm one of them.
我会出汗  放屁  打嗝
I sweat, I fart and I burp.
你不会又来一次吧
You're not gonna do that again, are you?
不会
No.
其实我觉得应该回到自己家人身边去了
In fact, I should probably get back to my family.
在这种对他们最艰难黑暗的时刻
In this, their darkest hour.
保罗
Paul.
对不起  亲爱的
Oh, I'm sorry, dear.
我只想体会下这世上另外一半人是怎样生活的
I just wanted to see how the other half lives.
晕
Oh.
我晕
Oh, man.
查莉呀  这下除了我之外所有家人都上今晚的新闻节目了哟
Hey, Charlie, so everyone except for me was on the news tonight,
现在他们正在上网看呢
And now they're all watching it on the Internet.
没错的  邓肯一家现在已经被广泛传播成为当季最红人了
That's right... the Duncans have gone viral.
我的天哪  我看上去像个小丑
Oh my gosh I look like a clown.
算了  至少你还讲话了
Well, at least you talked.
对啊  讲个没完没了的
And talked and talked...
别打击我了
Hey.
我的上相很酷呀
I look cool.
看吧  这就是我们家最和谐的一件事
See, that's the great thing about this family...
我们可以毫不在乎地取笑自己
We can laugh at ourselves.
希望你以后也会如此豁达
And hopefully you feel the same way.
当你长大后发现到那个
When you're older and realize
“全世界的人看过我放屁”的事实
"Everyone in the world has seen me pass gas."
我去开门
I'll get it.
嗨
Hi
好啊
Hey
我只是想来看看你好不好
I just wanted to make sure you were okay.
嗯  我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
对于我的父母  我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry about my parents.
哇  难得听到别人这样讲  感觉真好
Wow, it is really nice to hear that coming out of somebody else's mouth.
我在想明天我们也许可以就在你家学习
I was thinking maybe tomorrow we could study here.
比我家有意思多了
It's a lot more fun than my house.
真的吗  还是你只想让我好受才这样说的
Really? Or are you just saying that to be nice?
不  我是真心这样想  我家总是那么安静
No, I mean it. It's always so quiet at my house.
这里有喧哗但也有乐趣
Over here it's loud and fun.
还充满了各种各样的不同气味
And full of different smells.
好吧  那就在我家了
Okay, my house it is.
有没有可能是牛肉酱晚餐
Any chance of a sloppy Joe night?
哎呀  反正一定会有什么酱的
Oh, it'll be a sloppy something night.
那就明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
啊  等一下下
Oh hey, hold on a sec.
来看呀  查莉  这位就是我的男朋友斯宾塞哦
Hey, Charlie, this is my boyfriend Spencer.
你好  小查莉
Hi, Charlie.
他是不是很帅
Isn't he cute?
我希望有一天你也能找到个像他这么好的人
I hope someday you find somebody as great as him,
不过大概很难的  祝你好运了  查莉
But it might be tough. So good luck, Charlie.
不行  别看
Uh, nuh-uh.
哦  父亲  您弹的真是动人
Oh, father, that was lovely.
您在手指技巧上处理得太精巧了
Your finger-picking is so delicate.
你画的那副石榴静物图也是相当雅致  亲爱的
Almost as delicate as that pomegranate. That you're painting, dear.
晚餐在十五分钟内准备好
Dinner in 15 minutes.
今晚的餐色是法式红酒烩鸡配白芦笋
Tonight we're having coq au vin and white asparagus.
哎呀  我怎么还戴着下午茶装的珍珠链呢
Oh my, I still have on my afternoon pearls.
母亲  餐桌已经摆设妥当了
Mother, the table is set.
还有什么我可以效劳的吗
How else may I help you?
父亲  马匹已经刷洗并喂料完毕
Father, the horses have been groomed and fed.
看来我们的孩子吃了太多的豆子
It would seem our child is full of beans.
父亲  您真会逗我们开心
Father, how you make us titter.